RAPHAEL BRET MOUNET

INTERN **(**707)-741-1326

• DETAILS •

(707)-741-1326 rbretmounet@gmail.com

• LINKS •

Github

Linkedin

Website

• SKILLS •

SQL

HTML & CSS

Linux

PHP

Java

Matlab

Python

Git C++

Neural Networks

Unreal Engine

Windows OS

Mac OS

LANGUAGES

English

French

PROFILE

I am currently studying in college but my first few experiences in the professional space have been so positive that I can't wait to learn more in the real world and apply my skills. I am a quick learner and enjoy researching and learning new skills. I have a passion for tinkering with and building robots, looking at something complex only gets me excited to figure out how it works.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Intern at Johnson Space Center, Houston, Texas Area

January 2019 — Present

Created a steady-state visually evoked potentials brain-computer interface which involved creating a Matlab program that could use live electroencephalogram(EEG) data and use a recurrent neural network to predict the frequency a user was looking at. Also, collected and analyzed EEG data, using a DSI-24 headset, for training and testing the neural networks.

Cashier at Carl's Jr, Vallejo

September 2017 — June 2018

Worked at the drive-thru and front register taking orders, re-stocking ice in soda machines, sauces, cups, straws, napkins, replaced trash bags, brought trash to the dumpster, bagged and gave out orders, mopped/sweep floor, cleaned tables in the dining area, and cleaned bathrooms.

EDUCATION

B.S. Computer Engineer, Diablo Valley College, Pleasant Hill

August 2018 — March 2022

Currently attending a community college in pursuit of transferring to UC San Diego for a B.S. in Computer Engineering.

High School Diploma, Benicia High School, Benicia

August 2016 — May 2018

COURSES

Introduction to Programming C++, Diablo Valley College

January 2018 — May 2018

Adv Programming with C & C++, Diablo Valley College

August 2018 — December 2018

Assembly Prog/Comp Org, Diablo Valley College

January 2020 — May 2020

Prog Design & Data Structures C++, Diablo Valley College

August 2020 — December 2020

Python Data Structures, University of Michigan

November 2020 — November 2020

Using Python to Access Web Data, University of Michigan

December 2020 — December 2020

Using Databases with Python, University Of Michigan

December 2020 — December 2020